{
    "subject": "resource/Girlfriend_(B2K_song)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Girlfriend (B2K song)",
    "human_readable": "The label of Girlfriend (B2K song) is 'Girlfriend (B2K song)'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9271647334098816,
            "question": "What is the label of the B2K song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087699055671692,
            "question": "When was the B2K song 'Girlfriend' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8882253170013428,
            "question": "Is there a music video for the B2K song 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8561497330665588,
            "question": "What genre is the B2K song 'Girlfriend' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8442721366882324,
            "question": "What is the subject matter of the B2K song 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8038985133171082,
            "question": "What is the name of the B2K song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6151493191719055,
            "question": "Is 'Girlfriend' a song title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45666489005088806,
            "question": "Which musical group released the song 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3203989565372467,
            "question": "Who might have written the lyrics for 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31493479013442993,
            "question": "Where can you listen to the song 'Girlfriend'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Girlfriend (B2K song) is 'Girlfriend (B2K song)'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2493_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have written the lyrics for 'Girlfriend'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2493_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which musical group released the song 'Girlfriend'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2493_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Girlfriend' a song title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2493_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2493_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents contain information about the song \"Girlfriend\" by B2K, but they do not mention anything about it being labeled as \"'Girlfriend (B2K song)'\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information that suggests the label of the song \"Girlfriend\" by B2K is 'Girlfriend (B2K song)'. The documents provide details about the song, its release, and some related remixes but do not mention a specific label in that format."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The label of a song refers to the record company that releases it, not the title of the song itself.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The label of Girlfriend (B2K song) is actually Epic Records, as stated in the single infobox.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The label of a song is typically the name of the record company or music distributor that releases the song, not the title of the song itself.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}